{
    "id": "0803cebd3fec4461813807d3c2eda649",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The woman broke ……………………… in the middle of her speech.",
            "description": "Break down can mean cry.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please blow ……………………….. the candle.",
            "description": "To blow out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At last the storm has blown …………………………",
            "description": "Blow over can mean subside. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The opposition parties are planning to bring ………………………… a No-Confidence Motion against the Prime Minister.",
            "description": "To bring something forward is to introduce it for discussion. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused said that he couldn't call …………………………. the whole events.",
            "description": "To call something up is to recollect it. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers have called …………………….. the strike.",
            "description": "To call off something is to cancel it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The investigators tried to call ………………………….. crucial information from him.",
            "description": "To call forth is to elicit. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "forth",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The terrorist’s plan to blow ………………………… the bridge was foiled by police.",
            "description": "Blow up means explode.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is cut ……………………… for a job of this kind.",
            "description": "When you are cut out for something, you are perfectly suitable for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you work hard you will come …………………………. with flying colours.",
            "description": "To come off with flying colours is to be triumphant. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The publishers are bringing ……………………….. a new edition of this book.",
            "description": "To bring out is to publish.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The scheme fell ………………………….. for want of support.",
            "description": "Fall through = fail",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}